[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal did Arnold Schwarzenegger voice in the 2001 comedy movie Dr. Dolittle 2?", "correct_answer": "White Wolf", "incorrect_answers": ["Drunk Monkey", "Alligator", "Old Prison Bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company developed the computer game Command  Conquer: Generals?", "correct_answer": "Electronic Arts", "incorrect_answers": ["Microsoft", "NewGame Software", "Nintendo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film St. Elmos Fire, for her marriage with Howie, Wendy received from her dad a car made by what company?", "correct_answer": "Chrysler", "incorrect_answers": ["Ford", "Chevrolet", "Toyota"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately what amount of meat does an adult male lion\u2019s diet require per day?", "correct_answer": "15 lbs. (6.8 kg)", "incorrect_answers": ["10 lbs. (4.5 kg)", "5 lbs. (2.2 kg)", "25 lbs. (11 kg)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement, concerning the vision of owls is true?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Owls must turn their entire head to change views.", "Owls are far-sighted and unable to clearly see within a few inches of their eyes.", "Owls have binocular vision."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What element comprises more than half of Mercurys mass?", "correct_answer": "Iron", "incorrect_answers": ["Lead", "Nickel", "Carbon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the nationality of William III of England who was often called William of Orange?", "correct_answer": "Dutch", "incorrect_answers": ["French", "Spanish", "English"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The two types of Chinese Crested dogs are born in separate litters, they cannot come from the same litter.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important aspect did the townspeople of Rock Ridge forget to put in the fake town they built in Blazing Saddles?", "correct_answer": "People", "incorrect_answers": ["Horses", "Cattle", "The Town Hall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An early version of this instrument was invented by Bartolomeo Cristofori of Florence, who was employed by the Medici family.", "correct_answer": "The piano", "incorrect_answers": ["The crane", "The steam drill", "The plow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest active volcano on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Mauna Loa", "incorrect_answers": ["Mount Rainier", "Mount Etna", "Merapi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A lilac colored cow is the symbol of this brand of chocolate, a best-seller for Kraft Foods, created in 1901 in Neuch\u00e2tel, Switzerland by chocolatier Philippe Suchard.", "correct_answer": "Milka", "incorrect_answers": ["Nestle", "Svoge", "Lindt"]}]